Oh, Phoebe, are you still on hold?
哦，菲比，你還在等嗎？
I was supposed to call my dad back like two hours ago.
我本來應該在兩個小時前就回電給我爸爸的。
Oh, yeah, he clicked on.
哦，是的，他點選了。
He said call him as soon as you get a chance.
他說一有機會就打電話給他。
He's at Flimby's.
他在弗林比家。
What's Flimby's?
弗林比是什麼？
Oh, yeah, that's the word I use when I can't remember the real
哦，是的，當我記不起真實的情況時，我會用這個詞
thing.
事物。
Okay, hang up.
好的，結束通話。
That's it.
就是這樣。
Come on.
快點。
No, Rachel, that's what they want me to do.
不，雷切爾，這就是他們想要我做的。
My warranty expires tomorrow.
我的保固明天就到期了。
If I don't get through, they're not going to fix my crappy broken
如果我沒有透過，他們就不會修復我的蹩腳破損
phone for free.
免費電話。
I mean, we cannot let them win.
我的意思是，我們不能讓他們贏。
It's us versus them.
這是我們與他們的對抗。
Yes.
是的。
I say hang up.
我說掛了。
It's Chandler and us versus Monica and them.
這是錢德勒和我們對抗莫妮卡和他們。
Hey.
嘿。
Listen, I got to double check for tickets tonight.
聽著，今晚我得仔細檢查一下票。
Who got one?
誰有一個？
I have one.
我有一個。
I need two.
我需要兩個。
I'm bringing Pete.
我要帶皮特來。
My boyfriend.
我的男朋友。
I have a boyfriend now.
我現在有男朋友了。
Two it is.
是兩個。
Russ, how about you?
拉斯，你呢？
Yeah, I also need two.
是的，我也需要兩個。
Really?
真的嗎？
Who's number two?
誰是第二名？
One of the more difficult games sewer workers play.
下水道工人玩的較難的遊戲之一。
No, it's just this person.
不，只是這個人。
Like a date type person?
喜歡約會型的人嗎？
Yeah, kind of.
是的，有點。
It's this woman from work.
是這個下班的女人。
I hope that won't be too weird.
我希望這不會太奇怪。
Will it, Rach?
會嗎，瑞秋？
No.
不。
No, not at all.
不，一點也不。
I was actually going to bring someone myself.
其實我本來是想自己帶人來的。
But you said one ticket.
但你說的是一張票。
I meant me plus one.
我的意思是我加一。
Okay.
好的。
Did you guys mean you plus one?
你們的意思是加一嗎？
All right.
好的。
I'll see you tonight.
今晚見。
Okay.
好的。
Bye-bye.
再見。
Bye.
Bye-bye.
再見。
Okay.
好的。
I need a date.
我需要一個約會。
Oh, hey.
哦，嘿。
You guys are finally going to get to meet Kate.
你們終於要見到凱特了。
And I borrowed some of your cologne.
我借了一些你的古龍水。
I hope she likes it.
我希望她喜歡。
Joey, what are you doing?
喬伊，你在做什麼？
That's never going to happen.
那永遠不會發生。
She's seeing somebody.
她正在見某人。
Yeah, and I don't have any cologne.
是的，我沒有古龍水。
Green bottle next to the shaving cream.
刮鬍膏旁邊的綠色瓶。
Oh, we're medicine for the duck.
哦，我們是鴨子的藥。
You can
你可以
wear this.
穿這個。
Thanks.
謝謝。
Okay.
好的。
I'm setting the phone down.
我正在把電話放下。
But I'm still here.
但我還在這裡。
Just don't go anywhere.
只是別去任何地方。
I'm still here.
我還在這裡。
Don't switch or anything because I'm right here.
不要切換或做任何事情，因為我就在這裡。
Just one sec.
只需一秒鐘。
One sec.
一秒鐘。
One second!
一秒鐘！
Wait!
等待！
One second!
一秒鐘！
Phoebe?
菲比？
What?
什麼？
Monica, I'm scared!
莫妮卡，我害怕！
That's a sleeve, okay?
那是一個袖子，好嗎？
Yeah.
是的。
And we also have a speakerphone.
我們還有揚聲器。
Please stay on the line.
請保持通話。
Your call is important to us.
您的來電對我們很重要。
Anyway, you've got to hang up because we're going to be late.
不管怎樣，你得掛電話了，因為我們要遲到了。
Thank you for your patience.
感謝您的耐心等待。
You're the next caller.
你就是下一個來電的人。
Yes!
是的！
I'm the next caller!
我是下一個打電話的人！
You're going to have me hang up.
你會讓我結束通話電話。
Hey.
嘿。
Can you take a duck and a chick to the theater?
你能帶一隻鴨子和一隻小雞去劇院嗎？
Of course not.
當然不是。
Okay.
好的。
I just wanted them to hear it from somebody else.
我只是想讓他們從別人那裡聽到這個訊息。
All right, fellas.
好吧，夥計們。
Back to Nintendo.
回到任天堂。
Hey.
嘿。
Hey, Rach.
嘿，瑞秋。
Oh, hi.
哦，嗨。
How are you?
你好嗎？
Good.
好的。
Hey.
嘿。
So it looks like we're the first ones here.
所以看起來我們是第一批來這裡的。
Yeah, it looks that way.
是的，看起來就是這樣。
First ones here!
第一批在這裡！
Woo!
哇！
Oh, Tommy, this is Ross, Ross, Tom.
哦，湯米，這是羅斯，羅斯，湯姆。
Hey.
嘿。
Oh, I'm sorry.
哦，對不起。
This is Kaylin.
這是凱琳。
Hi.
你好。
Sorry.
對不起。
And Blake!
還有布萊克！
Okay.
好的。
I think I'm going to run to the ladies' room.
我想我要跑到女洗手間去。
Okay.
好的。
I'll join you.
我會加入你。
I'll get her.
我會去接她的。
Okay.
好的。
So, uh, well, this is, uh, this is awkward.
所以，呃，好吧，這，呃，這很尷尬。
Yeah?
是的？
Well, you know, because Rachel and I used to go out.
嗯，你知道，因為雷切爾和我經常出去玩。
Oh, I didn't know that.
哦，我不知道。
Oh.
哦。
Well, then, this is awkward.
那麼，這就尷尬了。
So what are you, uh...
那你是什麼，呃...
I think we're here.
我想我們到了。
Yeah.
是的。
Okay.
好的。
Uh, huh.
呃，呵呵。
Excuse me.
打擾一下。
I'm sorry.
對不起。
I think you may be in our seats.
我想你可能坐在我們的座位。
Um, no, I don't think so.
嗯，不，我不這麼認為。
Can we take a look at your ticket?
我們可以看一下您的票嗎？
Sure.
當然。
Yep.
是的。
Yeah.
See, this says D13, and, uh...
看，這上面寫著 D13，而且，呃...
Oh, well, I thought that, uh...
哦，好吧，我以為，呃...
You thought, huh?
你以為是嗎？
Yeah, well, that didn't really work out too well for it, did you?
是的，好吧，這對它來說效果不太好，是嗎？
Idiot!
笨蛋！
What are you, a moron, huh?
你是什麼人，白痴吧？
It says D13, okay?
上面寫著D13，好嗎？
Look, you're surrounded by even numbers.
看，你周圍都是偶數。
Does that give you some clue?
這能給你一些線索嗎？
Oh!
哦！
Oh, well, the usher must be right.
哦，好吧，引座員一定是對的。
What with all the training they go through.
他們經歷了這麼多的訓練怎麼辦？
Get out!
出去！
Here.
這裡。
Hey, man, you went to the aisle?
嘿，夥計，你去過道了嗎？
No, I'm good.
不，我很好。
What?
什麼？
There he is!
他在那兒！
Hey!
嘿！
So, so, what'd you think?
那麼，那麼，你覺得怎麼樣呢？
Almost as good as the play with the two naked girls on the
幾乎和兩個裸體女孩一起玩一樣好
seesaw.
蹺蹺板。
I wasn't in there.
我當時不在裡面。
I know.
我知道。
Oh, hey, hey, hey.
哦，嘿，嘿，嘿。
Listen, I want you to meet everybody.
聽著，我想讓你見見所有人。
Everybody, this is Kate.
大家好，這是凱特。
Excuse me.
打擾一下。
Hi.
你好。
Excuse me.
打擾一下。
Hi, sweetheart.
嗨，親愛的。
Hi.
你好。
Come.
來。
So that's the girl you like?
那麼，這就是你喜歡的女孩嗎？
I'm telling you, this guy Rachel is with, it's crazy, okay?
我告訴你，和瑞秋在一起的這個人，太瘋狂了，好嗎？
He viciously screamed at total strangers.
他對著完全陌生的人惡毒地尖叫。
I think he's bad news.
我認為他是個壞訊息。
Wait a minute, wait a minute.
等一下，等一下。
You don't like the guy Rachel's dating?
你不喜歡瑞秋約會的那個人？
Well, that's odd.
嗯，這很奇怪。
Oh, hey, Lauren.
哦，嘿，勞倫。
You guys, this is Kate's understudy, Lauren.
各位，這是凱特的替身，勞倫。
Oh, hi.
哦，嗨。
Hi.
你好。
Hey, gosh, you look so familiar.
嘿，天哪，你看起來好熟悉。
Oh, yeah, I ran into you in the hallway in your building.
哦，是的，我在你大樓的走廊上遇見了你。
It was right after I slept with Joey.
就在我和喬伊睡過。
He dumped me the next day.
第二天他就把我甩了。
So how'd you guys meet?
那你們是怎麼認識的呢？
Well, the short version is I pursued her for a couple of months.
嗯，簡單來說就是我追求了她幾個月。
Then I gave her a check for $20,000 and she was mine.
然後我給了她一張2萬美元的支票，她就是我的了。
Yeah, and in the long version, I dumped him for telling people the
是的，在長版本中，我拋棄了他，因為他告訴人們
short version.
簡短版本。
Joey, sweetheart, you were fabulous.
喬伊，親愛的，你太棒了。
Hey, you guys, this is my agent, Estelle.
嘿，大家，這是我的經紀人，艾斯特爾。
How do you do?
你好嗎？
Oh, you two girls were outstanding.
哦，你們兩個女孩很出色。
Did they have representation?
他們有代表嗎？
They weren't in the play.
他們沒有出現在劇中。
We're not actors.
我們不是演員。
Ah, what a shame.
啊，真可惜。
Because with her face and her chest, I could really put something together.
因為有了她的臉和胸部，我真的可以把一些東西放在一起。
Could I borrow it?
可以藉用一下嗎？
Hi.
你好。
Remember me?
記住帳號？
Hi, yeah.
嗨，是的。
Tommy's in line for the bathroom and someone just cut in front of
湯米正在排隊上廁所，有人插到了前面
him.
他。
I think he's gonna snap.
我想他會崩潰的。
Ross, I'm gonna go.
羅斯，我要走了。
Go?
去？
Why?
為什麼？
I don't know.
我不知道。
Could be because I don't feel like standing around all night waiting for
可能是因為我不想整夜站著等待
some guy who may or may not scream.
某個可能會尖叫也可能不會尖叫的人。
But Caelan, he definitely will scream.
但凱蘭，他肯定會尖叫。
Goodbye, Ross.
再見，羅斯。
Oh, go, bye.
噢，走吧，再見。
Here we go, people.
我們開始吧，朋友們。
Boxing Day.
節禮日。
The Lucille Hotel Theater.
露西爾酒店劇院。
Joey Tribbiani gives an uneven performance about Mr. Tribbiani is not the worst
喬伊·特里比亞尼 (Joey Tribbiani) 的表現參差不齊，特里比亞尼先生並不是最差的
thing in this production.
這個製作中的東西。
Yes!
是的！
Kate Miller's awkward and mannered portrayal is laughable.
凱特米勒（Kate Miller）笨拙而彬彬有禮的形象令人發笑。
Aha, here it is.
啊哈，就是這裡。
The Direction by Marshall Townend is...
馬歇爾湯恩德 (Marshall Townend) 的方向是…
Thank you, boys and girls.
謝謝你們，男孩們和女孩們。
You've ruined my life.
你毀了我的生活。
Please, stuff your talentless faces with my mother's crab cakes.
拜託，把我媽媽做的蟹餅塞到你們那張沒才華的臉上吧。
Excuse me!
打擾一下！
Does anyone mind if I save this?
有人介意我儲存這個嗎？
Hey.
嘿。
Oh, is the play over?
哦，戲結束了嗎？
Yeah, where were you?
是啊，你在哪裡？
Thank you for your patience.
感謝您的耐心等待。
You're the next caller.
你就是下一個來電的人。
You're the next caller five hours ago.
五小時前你就是下一個來電的人。
You must be going crazy.
你一定要瘋了。
Nah, kept myself busy.
不，讓自己忙起來。
Okay, yeah, I put your stuff in her room and her stuff in
好的，是的，我把你的東西放在她的房間，她的東西放在
your room.
你的房間。
Hey.
嘿。
You okay?
你還好嗎？
Fabulous.
太棒了。
Listen, drama critics, they're nothing but people who couldn't make it as
聽著，戲劇評論家，他們只不過是那些無法成功的人
actors.
演員。
You know what you should do?
你知道你該做什麼嗎？
Become a drama critic.
成為戲劇評論家。
I'm hurt!
我受傷了！
A plague!
一場瘟疫！
Both your houses!
都是你家的！
By the way, he dumped me tonight after he read my review.
順便說一句，他今晚在讀了我的評論後拋棄了我。
Oh, classy.
哦，優雅。
Yep.
是的。
I sure know how to pick him, huh?
我當然知道怎麼選他了，是嗎？
You know, I gave up a part on the soap for this.
你知道，我為此放棄了肥皂的一部分。
Wow.
哇。
Yeah, I, uh, I gave up a job, too.
是的，我，呃，我也放棄了工作。
Really?
真的嗎？
What?
什麼？
Uh, decline cats.
呃，拒絕貓。
Hey, tell you what.
嘿，告訴你什麼。
Let me walk you home.
讓我送你回家。
We'll stop by every newsstand and burn every copy of their Times in
我們會去每個報攤並燒掉他們的每一份《泰晤士報》
the Post.
郵報。
And where are the Post?
郵政在哪裡？
You didn't see the Post?
你沒看到貼文嗎？
No, you?
不，你呢？
No, why?
不，為什麼？
You really think these newspapers are just jealous of me?
你真以為這些報紙只是嫉妒我？
Absolutely.
絕對地。
You're talented and you're good-looking.
你很有才華，而且長得又帥。
You're sweet and cute.
你又甜又可愛。
I know.
我知道。
That's why they trashed me.
這就是他們毀掉我的原因。
Wait, wait, wait.
等等，等等，等等。
Wait a minute, wait a minute.
等一下，等一下。
What?
什麼？
I don't get you.
我不明白你的意思。
I mean, first, you hate me.
我的意思是，首先，你討厭我。
Then, you sleep with me.
那你就陪我睡吧。
Then, you want nothing to do with me.
那麼，你就不想跟我有任何關係了。
Now, you want me again.
現在，你又想要我了。
What, so you never went out with an actress before?
什麼，所以你以前從未和女演員約會過？
Kate, do you even like me?
凱特，你喜歡我嗎？
Of course I do.
我當然知道。
Well, so how come you blew me off?
好吧，那你怎麼把我趕走了？
You know, how come you were with him?
你知道嗎，你怎麼會跟他在一起？
I don't know.
我不知道。
Just, just do this.
只是，就這樣做。
I always have to pick, like, the smartest guy or the most talented
我總是必須選擇最聰明的人或最有才華的人
guy.
傢伙。
Why can't I just pick someone like you?
為什麼我不能選擇像你這樣的人呢？
Thanks.
謝謝。
You know what I mean.
你知道我的意思。
I mean, like, the sweetest guy.
我的意思是，最可愛的人。
Joe, you're just so...
喬，你真是…
You're so...
你真是…
So...
所以...
Okay, okay.
好吧，好吧。
There we go.
我們開始吧。
Let's get you up there.
讓我們帶你上去吧。
Come on.
快點。
Well, good night, Kate.
好吧，晚安，凱特。
Sweet dreams.
甜蜜的夢。
I'm gonna put this can right here in case you have to hurl.
我會把這個罐子放在這裡以防萬一你不得不扔。
Please stay on the line.
請保持通話。
Your call is very important.
您的來電非常重要。
You've been up for 24 hours.
你已經24小時沒睡了。
Go to sleep, honey.
去睡覺吧，親愛的。
This isn't healthy.
這不健康。
No, no, I'm fine.
不，不，我很好。
And you know why?
你知道為什麼嗎？
Because of all the riboflavin.
因為所有的核黃素。
Hey.
嘿。
Didn't you have that outfit on last night?
你昨晚沒穿那件衣服嗎？
Yeah.
是的。
I stayed at Kate's, but, uh, nothing happened.
我住在凱特家，但是，呃，什麼事也沒發生。
Yeah, last time I was at Pete's, we just watched a movie.
是的，上次我在皮特家，我們剛剛看了電影。
Of us.
我們的。
That we'd made earlier.
是我們之前做的。
I'm sorry, I can't help it.
對不起，我無能為力。
I have a boyfriend.
我有一個男朋友。
Hey, Phoebs, where were you?
嘿，菲布斯，你在哪裡？
I'm so, so sorry, Joey.
我非常非常抱歉，喬伊。
I am definitely gonna see your play.
我一定會去看你的戲的。
I swear, your play is very important to us.
我發誓，你的表現對我們來說非常重要。
Thank you for your patience.
感謝您的耐心等待。
Your play is the next play I'm gonna see.
你的戲就是我下一場要看的戲。
Anyway, how'd it go with Kate?
無論如何，凱特怎麼樣？
Oh, it was great.
哦，太棒了。
Yeah, I walked her home, and it was amazing how much we connected,
是的，我送她回家，令人驚訝的是我們之間的連結如此緊密，
you know?
你知道？
Then, uh, then she passed out.
然後，呃，然後她就昏過去了。
But then she woke up, yeah?
但後來她醒了，是嗎？
And we stayed up all night talking, and now we're, like, totally crazy
我們整晚都在聊天，現在我們簡直瘋了
about each other.
關於彼此。
Joey, you had the night.
喬伊，你度過了一個夜晚。
What?
什麼？
Yeah, when two people finally realize their feelings for each other, and they
是的，當兩個人終於意識到彼此的感情時，他們
talk for hours, and they learn all about the other person.
聊了幾個小時，他們就瞭解對方的一切了。
You think?
您認為？
Did you, like, learn about her family?
你瞭解她的家庭嗎？
Two brothers.
兩個兄弟。
One died.
其中一人死亡。
Yes!
是的！
This is from the woman at the bar.
這是酒吧裡那位女士寄來的。
Oh.
哦。
Sorry, she thought she was somebody else.
抱歉，她以為自己是別人。
What time is it?
現在是幾奌？
1.
7.15. Watch doesn't work.
7.15。手錶不起作用。
Tommy's supposed to be here soon.
湯米應該很快就會到了。
We're going to lunch.
我們要去吃午餐了。
Look, look, I wasn't gonna say anything to you, but...
聽著，聽著，我本來不想對你說什麼，但...
All right, I don't think you should be seeing Tommy anymore.
好吧，我認為你不應該再見到湯米了。
You don't?
你不這麼認為嗎？
No.
不。
The guy is mean.
這傢伙很卑鄙。
I mean, really mean.
我的意思是，真的。
I think you should stay away from him.
我認為你應該遠離他。
Hmm, or maybe I should stay away from all men.
嗯，或者也許我應該遠離所有男人。
No, it's not just because I'm jealous.
不，這不僅僅是因為我嫉妒。
I mean, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not jealous, okay?
我的意思是，我沒有，我沒有，我沒有嫉妒，好嗎？
It's...
這是...
Look, the guy, he screamed.
看，那個傢伙，他尖叫起來。
He actually screamed at this couple sitting in our seats.
他實際上對坐在我們座位上的這對夫婦尖叫。
Yeah, and at the end of the play, he got up, you know,
是的，在比賽結束時，他站了起來，你知道，
and he just started like, banging his hands together.
然後他就開始用力敲擊雙手。
Okay, fine, fine.
好吧，好吧，好吧。
You don't want to believe me?
你不想相信我嗎？
No, it's fine.
不，沒關係。
Ross, don't believe him.
羅斯，別相信他。
No one believe me.
沒有人相信我。
I'm Mr. Funny to you.
我對你來說是有趣的先生。
Mr. Funny.
滑稽先生。
Whoa!
哇！
Oh, sorry, Tommy.
哦，對不起，湯米。
What's in the cup, Ross?
羅斯，杯子裡有什麼？
Um...
嗯...
What is in the cup?
杯子裡有什麼？
Okay, it's coffee.
好吧，是咖啡。
Iced coffee?
冰咖啡？
Tell me it's iced coffee.
告訴我這是冰咖啡。
It's hot.
很熱。
Hot coffee!
熱咖啡！
You idiot!
你這個白痴！
You're gonna spill hot coffee all over me, huh?
你會把熱咖啡潑到我身上吧？
What are you, just a big, dumb, stupid, doofy idiot with a doofy
你是什麼，只是一個又大又笨又蠢又傻的白痴
idiot hairdo?
白痴髮型？
Huh?
啊？
What's your favorite thing about summertime?
夏天你最喜歡什麼？
Going to the beach.
去海灘。
When it stays light real late.
當天色很晚的時候。
Yeah.
是的。
Hey.
嘿。
Tommy.
湯米.
Say, what's your favorite thing about summer?
說說吧，夏天你最喜歡什麼？
Ooh.
哦。
I don't know.
我不知道。
Probably the, uh, smell of freshly cut grass.
可能是，呃，剛割下的青草的味道。
Oh, that's a good one.
哦，那是一件好事。
Sorry.
對不起。
Sorry I'm late.
抱歉我來晚了。
My doc and my chick had a fight.
我的醫生和我的女兒吵架了。
It was ugly.
太醜了。
Look, we have the curt for you, buddy.
聽著，我們為你準備了簡短的內容，老兄。
Come on, let's go.
來吧，我們走吧。
Let's go.
我們走吧。
Okay.
好的。
Vic!
維克！
Where have you been, baby?
寶貝你去哪裡了？
Where's Kate?
凱特在哪裡？
She's got a job in L.A. What?
她在洛杉磯有工作。什麼？
I've been waiting up all night for you.
我整晚都在等你。
Where have you been?
你去哪裡了？
Where have you been, Vic?
維克，你去哪裡了？
Hey, uh, go to the window.
嘿，呃，到視窗去。
I want to run down to the truck and show you something.
我想跑到卡車那裡給你看一些東西。
What do you got down there, Vic?
維克，你下面有什麼？
I got under that tarp.
我鑽到了防水布下面。
When is she leaving?
她什麼時候走？
Tonight.
今晚。
What are you doing?
你在幹什麼？
I'm coming up!
我來啦！
You hanging in there?
你還掛在那裡嗎？
Mm-hmm.
嗯嗯。
You doing okay?
你還好嗎？
Mm-hmm.
嗯嗯。
You listening to me?
你在聽我說話嗎？
Mm-hmm.
嗯嗯。
Okay.
好的。
If Pete calls again, and you don't put him through, I will kill
如果皮特再打來，而你又不給他接通，我就殺了他
you.
你。
Hey, mind if I use the phone?
嘿，介意我用一下電話嗎？
Oh, I'm fat, and I have weight.
哦，我很胖，而且我有體重。
Why don't you use ours across the hall?
為什麼不在大廳對面使用我們的呢？
Because she has problems.
因為她有問題。
Whoa, whoa!
哇哦！
Sorry, Tommy, I almost spilled this hot coffee on you.
抱歉，湯米，我差點把熱咖啡灑到你身上了。
Yeah, but you didn't.
是的，但你沒有。
No, but it's...
不，但這是...
It's hot.
很熱。
Ross, would you just stop it?
羅斯，你能停下來嗎？
It's getting really old.
真的是越來越老了。
I can't believe no one believes me.
我不敢相信沒有人相信我。
I do.
我願意。
I believe you.
我相信你。
You do, Pheebs?
你知道嗎，菲比？
Yeah, but I also believed her when she said I was next.
是的，但當她說我是下一個時，我也相信了她。
Ooh, hey.
哦，嘿。
Hey there, little fella.
嘿，小傢伙。
Mr. Fuzzy Man.
模糊人先生。
How you doing?
你好嗎？
Oh.
哦。
Ew.
呃。
Oh.
哦。
Ew.
呃。
Gross.
總的。
Idiot!
笨蛋！
Stupid little fuzzy yellow creature!
愚蠢的小毛茸茸的黃色生物！
Oh, look at me.
哦，看著我。
I'm so cute.
我真是太可愛了
I'm a little chick who's disgusting!
我是一個令人厭惡的小妞！
God, you're so stupid!
天哪，你真是太傻了！
How are you not yet extinct?
你怎麼還沒滅絕呢？
Quack, quack, quack, quack!
嘎嘎，嘎嘎，嘎嘎，嘎嘎！
What are you quacking about?
你在嘎嘎叫什麼？
Dumb Donald Dodo!
愚蠢的唐納德·多多！
Step away from the duck.
離鴨子遠一點。
Oh, sorry, little Mr. Chickadee.
哦，對不起，小山雀先生。
Saw you with Doody in my hand!
看到你手裡拿著杜迪！
Well, I guess we're not going out anymore.
好吧，我想我們不會再出去了。
Man!
男人！
Joey.
喬伊。
Hey.
嘿。
I'm so glad I caught you.
我很高興抓住了你。
I couldn't find you before.
之前我找不到你。
What's going on?
這是怎麼回事？
What's all this about L.A.? They still want me for general hospital.
洛杉磯到底是怎麼回事？他們仍然想要我去綜合醫院。
But what about us?
但我們呢？
Last night was wonderful.
昨晚真是太棒了。
But I can't stay here just for you.
但我不能只為了你留在這裡。
Well, so stay for the museums.
好吧，那就留下來參觀博物館吧。
I'm sorry.
對不起。
Joey, on stage.
喬伊，在舞臺上。
Well, can you at least stay to the end of the play?
好吧，你至少能堅持到比賽結束嗎？
I mean, I'll go to the airport with you.
我是說，我會跟你一起去機場。
I want to say goodbye.
我想說再見。
Where are you, Vic?
維克，你在哪裡？
My flight's in an hour.
我的航班還有一個小時。
I gotta go.
我得走了。
Vic!
維克！
In a minute!
一分鐘後！
So this is it, Victor?
就是這樣嗎，維克多？
Yeah, I guess it is.
是的，我想是的。
Listen, I, uh, I gotta say goodbye, and I gotta say it quick,
聽著，我，呃，我要說再見，我要快點說，
because this is killing me.
因為這簡直要了我的命。
One thing you gotta know is that I will never forget you.
你必須知道的一件事是我永遠不會忘記你。
But you got things you have to do now, and so do I.
但你現在有你必須要做的事情，我也是。
And so...
所以...
I'm gonna get on this spaceship.
我要登上這艘太空船
And I'm gonna go to Gloggon 7 in search of alternative fuels.
我要去 Gloggon 7 找替代燃料。
But when I return, 200 years from now, you'll be long gone.
但當我回來時，200年後，你早已不在了。
But I won't have aged at all.
但我根本不會變老。
So you tell your great-great-granddaughter to look me up.
所以你讓你的曾曾孫女來找我。
Because, Adrian, baby, I'm gonna want to meet her.
因為，阿德里安，寶貝，我想見她。
Phoebe, it's been two days.
菲比，已經兩天了。
Yeah, I know.
是的，我知道。
Oh, good thing it's one of those 801 numbers, right?
哦，幸好這是 801 號碼之一，對吧？
Phoebe, 800 is toll-free.
菲比，800 是免費電話。
801 is Utah.
801 是猶他州。
No, no, no, no.
不，不，不，不。
It has to be 800, because all those big companies have 800 numbers.
一定是800，因為那些大公司都有800個號碼。
Every...
每...
Yeah, every big Utah-based company has one.
是的，猶他州的每一家大公司都有一個。
Phoebe, sorry.
菲比，對不起。
I'm so sorry.
我很抱歉。
I will pay you back.
我會還給你。
And yet she's still not hanging up the phone.
但她仍然沒有結束通話電話。
Hang it up.
掛起來。
Hang up the phone.
結束通話電話。
Fine, fine.
很好，很好。
Oh, oh.
哦，哦。
What?
什麼？
Well, I think I broke it.
好吧，我想我打破了它。
That's all right.
沒關係。
Here's the number you can call.
這是您可以撥打的電話號碼。
Oh.
哦。